Good morning. Hey, Ahmed. I started to kind of like have a little bit of a panic moment this morning, knowing that I'm going on a book tour and I was saying to myself, man, it's not it's not like the last time.
It's not like the last time. And and and like I felt myself starting to spin my wheels about how to create a version of success that mirrored the last time I was out on the road, mirrored the last time I released something.
And then I'm sorry. Now I got to start over. Now I got to start over. OK, can you hear me now? Let me know if you can hear me. OK, so I I had started spinning my wheels on how do I make this book tour successful?
You know, like the last time I was out on the road and and how do I make it possible to meet these previous standards?
And then I had to check myself because nothing is the same. And that is the truth.
And so when I say truth is my religion. It's because I have a spiritual practice.
But it's the truth that really does set me free and grounds me and lets me release the energy.
It releases me from putting my energy into spaces that are not valid, that are not valuable.
And. I don't think y'all understand how far ahead my thinking is, because.
So many times I get frustrated by just so far behind the thinking is, because I see folks that are still talking about, you know, they see ICE agents, they see National Guardsmen, they see FBI attacking people and their response is.
They should lose their choice. They should lose their job.
Someone just said, can you define the truth to you? What are you talking about?
What are you talking about? There is no definition of the truth for me.
There is the truth. Capital T, capital H, capital E.
The truth. It's not subjective. It's not subjective.
There is no the truth for me and the truth for you.
That's why I hate when people say I'm speaking my truth, because it suggests that the truth is like individually attached.
Your experiences, your your experience is individually attached.
And so when we say my truth, I know that that's what it's supposed to mean.
But it gets it gets subverted into perspective.
And it's like, no, the truth is not perspective.
The truth is the truth. Your perspective of the truth is what it is.
So I had to I had to check myself.
Because no, Amanda, your book tour is not going to be the same as anything else you've done.
Nothing is the same.
Nothing is going to be the same.
We are in a cycle and we are in a constant of change right now at a rapid, rapid pace.
And I find myself having to ground myself in knowing that.
And that being that which comforts me, like knowing it is what's OK, so I don't know about your mother-in-law and I don't know about their involvement.
And you're spamming my page now.
So, you know, that's the type of things that I had to really check myself on and remind myself of to calm myself down.
And that's why I say truth is religion.
You're asking how do we properly mobilize?
And it's like if you're asking me that on Instagram Live, then you're not even trying.
If you're asking me on Instagram Live how to, that's why I know people be kind of full of it.
Because it's like if you're asking me on IG, then that means that you have not identified those in your actual physical community who do this work.
And there are people in every community who do mobilization work all the time, all the time.
So it's like asking me whatever, you know, what, how do we mobilize?
It's like there are people physically mobilizing all the time.
I'm not an organizer.
Also, I see people saying like, oh, you need to be the leader.
And I'm like, hold on, I got to block people.
And we have to like, like we have to also know that there's different forms of leadership.
Like there's different forms of leadership.
So thank you, Ken G-K-O-V.
Thank you.
Like people be coming out here.
Let me tell you something.
When I was, I did like a talk with Dick Gregory and he ended up yelling at me and cursing me out.
And I cursed him out back and I left the room.
And that was the last time we saw each other.
But I understand now why he cursed me out, because it's like, stop, get something out.
Like, and he was like trying to talk about something.
And I'm asking questions.
And he was like, God damn it.
But I get it.
You know, now I get it.
Like, stop trying to ask.
But like, just, you know, he was trying to talk and I needed to just, I needed to just be quiet.
I needed to just listen, you know, to just listen.
So I get it now.
And now I've become an old man.
Now I've become an old man.
But I really had just come on here to just, to share because I, you know, I'm, I'm, I find myself like you're, you're in this transition from the past to the present.
You don't even know what the future is.
You're just in this transition from the past to the present.
And you're constantly trying to recreate the past and the present.
And the reality is you cannot, you cannot, you cannot recreate the past and the present.
It's, it's literally impossible because the present is, is never what it was yesterday.
So you should always be creating in the present.
And that difference can be different, right?
Like that, that shift of the change from the past to present can be very much, you know, a chasm or an inch.
And right now I feel like it's a, it's a chasm.
And I find myself having to build a bridge over that chasm and the bridge over that chasm is truth.
I don't even know why I'm emotional right now.
There's a lot coming.
Um, and the reason I get frustrated on the internets is because I know that we are, I know that I'm amongst a people who have been effectively propagandized.
We talk about Israel, but Americans are sociopaths and psychopaths as well.
We fail to see our role or our way of living in that practice, but it is why we are unable to actually mobilize.
And I, I, you know, when people started saying, oh, I'm the 92%, like we're sitting this one out, we're sitting this one out.
At first I was annoyed more so because it was like, did you think voting was like it and now you're done?
Now I realize though that at its core, it just annoyed me because you just don't sit out in justice.
That's not a strategy to me.
There's ways to still be in resistance without putting your physical body out there because that would be a bad strategy.
But the idea of, oh, we've done everything.
We've done all the work.
Um, just, it just bothered me because it assumed that, well, actually, I mean, it, it, it,
it actually proves the fact that this, the, the, this country, this version of the world that we're in is coming to a close.
It's coming to a close.
And, um, you know, I don't think people grasp that.
Peoples come to an end all the time and countries and systems, they come to an end all the time.
Um, and it is the, the belief that we should exist because we're better that has allowed us to actually uphold a system that is deeply harmful.
So it's that what I mean.
That's what I mean when I say the truth is a religion, because when you understand that, when you understand the truth of things, it allows you to ground your belief in what you exist in.
Um, and that's what you, that's what you move from.
That's how you live.
So, you know, like there's people in here say, still talking about voting, not voting is not a logical strategy.
I, again, you are talking about things on a very surface plane right now.
A lot of you all are, you're, you're talking about things on a very, very surface plane.
You're literally talking about getting on a plane and it will, your, your guidance of what to do will require you to go deeper.
You're required.
Like, that's what I'm trying to tell you.
The guidance of, of what to do is not going to be about analyzing an election.
The guidance of what to do is not going to be about solely analyzing, you know, other countries to get citizenship in.
I'm not saying that that is not a part of vision.
However, so much of our, so much of our exploration and vision building is so shallow because it only goes to the depth of how do I individually, or how does my family survive?
That's how far y'all go.
And so you ask questions about voting and, you know, it's like, yeah, that's a conversation.
That's not the conversation I'm having right now on this Sunday morning.
That is incredibly surface.
And that's every conversation that we're seeing on the news.
All these surface conversations.
That's why I stopped going on mainstream media.
Because all these people talk about is basic conversations about the last 24 hours.
That's all they talk about.
And even when they try to get accountability, they never get it.
And it never means anything because they never push for it because they don't want to lose their job.
Imagine if everybody just said, fuck it, I'm losing my job.
Imagine.
Imagine if everybody just said, screw this.
Screw this.
What are they going to do?
They're going to kick everybody out?
The house?
The homes?
How?
What are they going to do?
They're going to fine everybody?
So what?
Don't nobody got no money?
They're going to close the grocery stores?
No, they're going to lower the prices.
If everybody said, fuck you, you won't do that.
Because the shallow analysis tells you no.
If we made money worthless, it wouldn't be worth it.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
But for so many people, their worth is attached to the money.
And that's the shallow analysis.
Your analysis will only go as deep as it allows you to maintain your status quo, to maintain your monetary function, to maintain your position.
And so I had to realize that, yes, Amanda, you are trying to go on a book tour.
You might not sell the books that you normally would sell.
You might not have the attendance you normally will have because folks don't got it.
And also because some folks have said, I'm not going to have it.
And I got to eat that.
And enjoy it.
And understand that that is a part of the process.
That's a part of the movement.
And like, suggestions.
You're pissing suggestions.
It's telling you, go forward.
And you motherfuckers will say, so then what do you suggest we do?
Don't even ask me, why are you yelling?
This is, why are you maddening?
Maddening.
Like, literally.
Who can't even identify solutions being told to them.
So what do you do?
If it's too early for you, Callie, no one is asking you to be here.
Nobody's taller.
Frustrating.
This is an influencer that I can just say shit to you.
Fuck you.
No.
Influencer.
I'm an actual leader.
I'm an actual thought leader.
I'm an actual philosopher.
I put my shit on the line all the fucking time.
And the folks on here are so close in security that they cannot even muster up respect
for someone who respects them.
It is maddening.
Maddening.
So, being plain, but keeps trying to talk like we are, and we're not going to perform.
No, it's not.
It's not, fuckers.
Wait till they start shooting indiscriminately into the groups of people that are rightfully
processing.
Wait.
It's coming.
And we're not going to be ready.
We're not.
It's coming.
And people are caught up about yelling.
Like, this is the society I'm in.
Can only black people say dumb shit.
Like, oh, we're done working, et cetera.
That's why I wrote What Would the Ancestors Say?
Our ancestors would be absolutely mortified at the way that we have been castrated and sterilized
out of resistance.
They are probably disgusted.
Look at these clowns.
Look at y'all.
A lot of people commit suicide because they're like, what is the point?
They're like, what is the point?
That's why.
I know because I've been there before.
Because they're like, what's the point?
What is the point?
They're like, why, why, why, why am I in pain all the goddamn time?
What's the point?
And so often they're in pain all the goddamn time because they just can't align with this
world because this world isn't trying to align with them.
This world isn't trying to align with each other.
And you're just like, what's the point?
What are you doing here?
Anywho, I don't feel like being a public figure on the internet today.
I just realized that in this moment because there is not, there just isn't enough.
There just isn't enough.
And that's what I mean by the shallow analysis.
So I hope that you all will, will push yourself to, to be more than what you were yesterday
because you're going to need to be.